I have 100 shares
of ICICI LBRD
at ₹1500. I have this IPO since the time of IPO.
This
IPO is very old. I have it since the IPO came seven-eight years ago
and this is
my average share at ₹1500. I have 100
shares. We are
ICICI Lomar, so I want to know its opinion.
I want to hold long term.  I want to
hold this for the next 10 years.
But will it
give returns, go up or remain here?
Ok.  Definitely, its IPO came around 2017
and its listing was seen around 680,
after that
we have seen a decent amount that a
decent rally has been seen in it.  But your
question is how much higher does it have the potential to go from here.  The
purchase
is for Rs 1500 and 100 shares are currently
in your portfolio.  Today,
even in a falling market, we are seeing a good momentum
in ICC LBT.
Amit ji, what do you think?  What does the Treasury look like going forward
?  If we look at this time, a
profit of around ₹400 per share is
visible.  What
numbers can we expect to see next?  Should it be held
or whatever little profit there is should be locked in,
ICICI Lar should be held not partially
because if we look at the weekly charts, the
stock is at a good support, there was
a run up in this stock, after that it went into a little
sideways consolidation but overall it
is positive, consolidation is
not a problem as of now, their view is
extremely long term, so
put a stop loss of 1800, if you say that
when will a bullish trend be
formed here, that will only happen
once the stock trades above 1960 1975 levels, if the
stop loss of 1800
is sustained, then I think that slowly
and steadily near
term targets of 2100 2150 are possible here.
OK, the advice is to hold ICICI LMBT,
we are seeing a lot of momentum here.
Today in fact the entire insurance space
is trading with a rally.  So we are
looking at the target till 2150.